The Clover Kingdom, in this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world,
and to become the next Wizard King.
The Clover Kingdom, in this video,
The Clover Kingdom.
What do you think?
Let's start this world
Even I can't help this world
All I need is getting strong
We can catch the game
Make it up to the end of the day
All I need is getting strong
We can catch the game
It's feeding time
I hope you guys are hungry
What are you doing there, Austin?
You really have to be so loud this early in the day
The noise really puts a damper on my morning dump
Quit messing around with my pets and let's head out
Huh? We going somewhere, Captain?
Yeah
We're supposed to be learning about the devils, remember?
We'll start with the curse
The one that they call Weg
That should give us a couple of clues to go on
Okay
You should come with us
Sure
Please forgive me, Sol
I let that elf take over my body
Let my squad down
I failed as a captain
No, Char
None of what happened was your fault
I may not have been possessed
But I still couldn't fix it
As much as I hate to admit it
The Black Bull's captain really saved our skin
Yami saved us?
My goodness
By the way, don't call me Char
As I keep telling you, it's Captain
You got it, Char
And yeah, he did a really good job
So I guess he isn't all that bad for a man
He's still gross
Besides, you could kick his butt any day
Wait a minute
This means that I didn't dream all those things
They actually happened while I was possessed
You did well, human
In my memories, Yami was so close to me
I can't believe all that was real
But I enjoyed fighting with you
Yami Sukihiro
Well, look at you, Charlotte
Turning all nice and honest at the end
That's sweet
I admit, I may be a little awkward
But not as awkward as she is
The details are a little fuzzy when I look back on it
But I'm fairly certain it went something like that
Oh dear
Does that mean that Yami already knows about my feelings for him?
No, that can't be true
Uh, Char, heads up
What is it, Sol?
Hey
The Captain of the Black Bulls is here to see you
No
He's here
Yami
I mean, what can I do for you?
These are for you, prickly princess
Came to see how you're doing
No
I do not have the mental or emotional capacity to be around him right now
Sol, get rid of him like you normally would
Oh crap, what should I do?
I guess the guy did save your life and all that
So maybe I won't run him off this time
Sol
How's the recovery process been going?
You okay, Char?
Well, I can't stay in bed forever
Oh no, my face probably looked so stupid when I said that
Try to calm down, Charlotte
You can handle this
Just don't push yourself too hard
You've always been the stubborn type and you're too awkward to ask for help
Awkward
Not to mention you're troublesome
Troublesome
But good to see you're all right
Oh, and if you don't mind
There's something I've been wanting to ask you
What?
Something he wants to ask me?
Oh my
I wonder if it's about that
You kind of brought it up before
What's he going to say?
See, you being under that crazy spell got me wondering
Oh no, what did I say?
I was hoping you could elaborate a little bit more
Give me all the fine details
I think it was
A forbidden curse?
What the heck did he say?
I wonder if he had a chance to ask her about Weg yet
Aw, come on
What are you acting all scared about?
Just relax
Please, I don't want to
I know somewhere fun we can go
After all, the kingdom's a mess lately
So we've got to stick together, right?
My lady said no!
Um, thanks for your help, ma'am
Ah, ah, ah
Ah, ah
Ah
Oh dear
That could have knocked me out
Thank you, miss
Ah, ah
Ah
A burglar
Great work
You
Hey, stop
You're headed straight for the river
I didn't realize forbidden magic was such a touchy subject for her
Please, Char
Come back
Char
Great
Now I've done it
Why am I always like this
I couldn't be honest with Yami
After that display, he probably thinks I'm insane
But becoming strong was the only way that I could endure the curse on House Roselay
She's had another fine showing
Yeah, she may be a newcomer, but she's obviously really powerful
Not to mention drop-dead gorgeous
Miss Charlotte
I'd be honored to make you my bride
No
Marry me instead, please
I quickly learned that men were all talk and couldn't be trusted
Anyone who can't defeat me cannot hope to handle my curse
Over time, I lost control of it
What the hell?
It's the curse on House Roselay
There's no hope
It's too strong
I can't stop it
At this rate, the village
Damn it
So pitiful
So shameful
Forgive me
Father
Mother
You really made a mess of things, huh?
Made me spill the pasta I was eating all over the place
Yami Sukuhiro
How could I let him see me in this sorry state?
I am defeated
I'm not a fan of chicks who prance into battle acting all smug when they have no reason to be
I prefer women who are strong
But you can lean on someone else every once in a while
You know how you can find lots of other strong people to lean on?
By joining the Magic Knights
Yami rescued me when my life was in turmoil
Unable to admit that
I've continued fighting as the captain of an all-woman Magic Knight Squad
As though nothing had happened
Enough
Now is the time
So why did you call us all here, Char?
Is it bad?
What's wrong, Captain?
As all of you are aware
The Blue Rose Knights are a group of female warriors who pride ourselves
On demonstrating strength and valor without the help of men
Once I say this
I am prepared to resign as your captain
So
Now
This is the truth
I have feelings
That I cannot ignore
I like Yami
I never wanted this to happen
But no matter how hard I try to resist
I still think about him constantly
There's just no changing it
I am hopelessly in love with Captain Yami
Whoa
Really?
I knew it
They feel betrayed
I'm such an utter disgrace of a captain
How romantic
Please support you, Captain
Whoa
This is just like Beauty and the Beast
I hope you guys get married soon and have a bunch of babies
And it's cute that you're both captains
I should tell you
I have a boyfriend too
We've been dating in secret this whole time
What?
Oh yeah, so do I
It's been really hard to hide
What?
I'm taking two
Yeah, so am I
So why don't you ask him out on a date?
What, just like that?
You got this, Captain
You're beautiful
You can have any guy you want
What?
But you can't chicken out
You're gonna have to make the first move
Or he won't know you're interested
Wait, interested?
You know
Tell him you want his bod
Oh hey
Maybe there's a super romantic restaurant you guys could try
The atmosphere at night is a real mood setter
You don't need to worry
If he doesn't like you back
Then there's something wrong with him
But he totally will, I promise
You have a lovely cool complexion, Captain
And you're summer
So you usually look your best in pinks and pastels
Wow
You really do have incredible skin, you know
Can you tell me your skin care secrets?
Ooh, how about this?
Let's try our rose color
Go, tell him
Do you think I should?
Confess your love
I don't know
Fine, I'll do it
I'll tell him how I feel
If you girls insist
Hold on, Char
Maybe just think about the consequences
It kind of feels like I just walked straight into a hen house
We'll be out of here in no time, okay?
Wow
So this is the Blue Rose Knight's headquarters, huh?
It's such a pretty place
What the hell are you doing?
Talk about terrible timing
There's no time like the present, Captain
You need to go over there and talk to him right now
Like, stop
Ask him if he wants to go out on a date
He's got it, Captain
That's close enough
Um, Yami
I want, that is
I'd like to
Uh
Talk louder
He can't hear you at all
This is so cute
Um, why are you mumbling like a crazy person now?
You sound like Gordon
Look, for what it's worth, I know how you feel
What?
I've known it all along
This is the moment
Your key is really something else
Charlotte
You can't stand the sight of me, can you?
You wish I was dead
Huh?
You didn't have to scream and run away like that
I may be all tough on the outside, but I have feelings too, you know
You and I have known each other for a long time
Would it kill you to stay put for a sec and listen to what I have to say?
What an oblivious idiot
She's doomed
How is she supposed to work up the courage now?
No
That's not
I'm so hopeless
I can't get the right words to come out
At this rate, you'll completely misunderstand what I mean
I'm not so sure, Captain Yami
It doesn't seem to me like she hates you
I don't recall asking your opinion on the matter, Mr. Suspended Senate
Look, the way that she's acting right now
It kind of reminds me of Noelle
Huh?
Which means she doesn't hate you, she just really trusts you
I think
And that makes it harder for her to be honest about her feelings
I learned that too a while back
Let me get this straight
So you figured out that Noelle trusts you or whatever
And it didn't change anything for you?
Shouldn't you be embarrassed?
Nope, not one bit
Because we're squad mates
And we've been through a lot of tough situations together
Yeah, Noelle's a complicated girl
But hey, we make it work
Don't worry, Captain
Just because you have trouble expressing your feelings
Doesn't mean you're a failure or anything
I think you're awesome
You and Captain Yami are still comrades, right?
He understands you
Who said you could put your grubby little hands on my shark?
Hold on a second
It looks like you've been blessed with some insightful subordinates
Nah, that one's less of a blessing and more of a curse
Asta, was it?
I should mention, I'm terribly sorry
When I was possessed, I know I caused a lot of trouble
No, it's fine
Everybody knows it's not your fault
You better show some respect, you puny scumbag
You said you wanted to discuss something, right?
So perhaps we could talk over dinner
Sure
Whatever will get you to answer my damn questions
Oh no, what am I going to do if Char ends up dating that guy?
Now then, what is it?
I just wanted to ask you something
Ask me anything
It's personal
Go ahead, I'm ready
What's the deal with that rose curse of yours?
Where'd it come from?
What's the matter?
Thank goodness
I'm so glad they didn't get together
I do feel kind of bad for Char though
Since she didn't get a chance to say how she feels
Wait a minute
Is that all?
That's what you wanted to talk about?
What were you expecting?
Curse you for getting my hopes up
Sorry
I'm only asking because the Wizard King ordered me and the Black Bulls to conduct an investigation into the ways of the devils
See, the kid's in a little bit of hot water and that crackpot judge with the scales is just itching to execute him for it
And since I'm his captain, I'm doing whatever I can to clear his name
It started when a powerful curse mage who held a deep-seated grudge against my family
Decided to cast a deadly spell
Its effect was like nothing in this kingdom and breaking it was impossible
Forbidden magic changes everything
Even the shape of the world
The curse activated when I was 18 years old
It not only affected the quality of my magic, but it altered my very soul
It's extremely likely that this curse used power from another realm
I thought as much
However, there's still a lot that I don't know
Fair enough
Thanks
I'm sorry
I suppose I wasn't very helpful
But if you're curious about forbidden curses
There's someone, a member of your own squad
Who's been affected far more severely than I have
One of my guys
All my closest friends
I'm so happy to have such wonderful company
Little girl
Like me
What can i talk about?
And when I was 15 years ago
You can K О Breach
And you know what you've accomplished
You know what I mean
Is it?
Do you know what I mean
蘇る記憶が 影を広げた
まだ止まない雨 居場所を示す
足跡はやがて 消えてしまうから
新しいページを今開こう
恐れずに 先頭で旗を振ろう
向かいが強いほど 高くまで飛べるから
Just take my hand 今日を生きる君に
明日が待っている
P...practice?
I'll practice confessing my love
This is humiliating
If it helps me get the words out
Right
Oyami
Your eyes sparkle like diamonds
They mesmerize me
They're so bright and so pure
I am desperately in love with you, Yami
I love you too, prickly princess
Now kiss me
Oh my, I thought you would never ask
Hey Char, what are you up so late for?
Wait, it was just a question!
That man...
I was hoping he would at least take the hint
But I suppose that's one of his charms
Black Clover, page 127
Clues
One day my thorns will pierce his heart
Up野症
Oh my gosh...
製おう
Jill
One day my son
Of the harblow
Oh my God
My Daddy
Look how love out there
Life at the boat
tit right in my life
That's already with me
What you took to do...